JASMINE DON

jasminedon96@gmail.com // www.linkedin.com/in/jasmine-don

EDUCATION

UCLA 2014-2017 English & Creative Writing B.A.

SKILLS

GPA: 3.70

Manuscript Coverage

Substantive Editing and Proofreading

Content Scheduling

AP, Chicago, MLA Style

Microsoft, Adobe and Google Suite

Web Publishing

Fiction and Comedy Writing

AWARDS & PUBLICATIONS

Westwind Journal Contributor (2017)

FPS Productions Pilot Script Competition Finalist (2017)

May Merrill Miller Award for Fiction Finalist (2017)

> David Sedaris Humor Writing Contest Winner (2016)

SUMMARY

Recent college graduate looking to work in writing, editing and publishing. Background includes fiction, screenwriting, journalism, comedy, theater and film studies. 3 years of managing and writing print and digital publications. 2 years of administrative experience.

EXPERIENCE

Charlotte Gusay Literary Agency, Los Angeles CA **Editorial Assistant** (Jun 2017 - Oct 2017)

- Critiqued clients' novel manuscripts, non-fiction proposals and screenplays.
- Rolled phone calls, responded to queries and managed submission paperwork and agency mail.

The Westwood Enabler, UCLA **Editor-in-Chief** (Oct 2014 - Jun 2017)

- Managed publication schedules for a team of 30 writers and copy editors.
- Wrote and edited articles for a comedy magazine about politics, college life, and current events.

Enrou, Culver City CA

Content Development Intern (Aug 2016 - Dec 2016)

- Launched online lifestyle magazine for a startup focused on sustainable, ethical e-commerce.
- Oversaw creative direction for all articles, ensuring that content reflected Enrou's brand and voice.
- Coordinated projects between in-house departments, external contributors, and interviewees.

Daily Bruin, UCLA

Radio News Intern (Sep 2015 - Dec 2015)

- Produced radio news segments for university newspaper.
- Recorded and edited student interviews.

FEM Newsmagazine, UCLA

Staff Writer (Oct 2014 - Jun 2015)

- Wrote news and opinion articles about gender, social media trends and entertainment.